https://poemsonly.com/main/privacy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
This privacy statement is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our web site.
It will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices, and the needs of our visitors.
This statement covers the following topics:
Information Collected and How it is Used
Personal Information and Choice
Public Access to Information
Security
Disclaimer
E-Mail Privacy Warning
Contact Information
When you browse our Web site, you do so without revealing your identity. Personal information, including your E-mail address, is not collected without your knowledge.
The use of and access to your personal information is restricted to those employees who need to know that information to provide services or support to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and
procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.
PoemsOnly.com does not divulge personal information collected or information disclosed voluntarily, but we may be required to do so pursuant to State or Federal law.
If you believe that your personal information is being used for a purpose other than that which was
intended when submitted, please contact us.
You may choose whether to provide personal information online. “Personal Information” is information about a natural person that identifies a specific individual. Personal information includes such things as an individual’s name, email address, and account password. A domain name or Internet protocol address is not considered personal information.
We do not collect personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You may choose not to provide personal information online. Your choice not to participate in this activity will not impair your ability to browse this Web site and read or view any information posted on this
site.
E-Mail Privacy Warning
E-mail is not a secure communication’s medium. Personal information sent via the Internet can be intercepted. You may, therefore, wish to reconsider the advisability of sending messages that contain highly sensitive or personal information to this Internet address.
